https://doleinstitute.org/site-policies/

Follow Us
HOMEGET INVOLVED
Programs
Dole Institute Program ScheduleDole Leadership PrizeDole LectureElizabeth Dole Women in Leadership LecturePresidential Lecture SeriesDole Fellowship ProgramPost-Election Conference
For Students
Student Advisory BoardDiscussion GroupsPizza & PoliticsDole Internship Assistance ProgramRobert E. Hemenway Public Service AwardRobert J. Dole Service to Country AwardYouth Civic Leadership InstituteDole Public Service ScholarshipCivic Engagement Essay Contest
Tours and Learning
K-12 EducationPublic Learning and ToursCivic Engagement & LearningEaster Egg Roll with Dole
Civic Engagement Tools
Political GlossaryVoting ResourcesMy Elected OfficialsCivic EngagementsGreat Minds Think Alike
Veterans Database
Submit Photos of WWII Veterans
Become a FriendCalendar of EventsVideosFor Researchers
VISIT
About
MissionHistoryBuildingStaffBoard of Advisors
Visit
AccessibilityFacility InformationSpecial Exhibits
News & Press
Annual ReportMedia ResourcesNews Releases
ABOUT BOB DOLE
Timeline of LifeA Legacy of LeadershipQuotesShare Your Bob Dole Story
LIVE STREAMING
SUPPORT US
VIDEOS
GET UPDATES
Make A Donation
You are now being directed to the University of Kansas Endowment Association Web site.
All donations made to the Dole Institute through the KU Endowment site are secure and used exclusively for the Dole Institute.
×
Dole Institute of Politics > Site Policies
Site Policies
DoleInstitute.org is committed to protecting the privacy and security of visitors to our website. Outlined below is our online privacy policy for personal information collected through this website. If you have questions about this policy, please let us know.
Collection and disclosure of information:
DoleInstitute.org collects some personal information (that is, information that can be directly associated with an individual) in order to engage on issues. DoleInstitute.org also collects names and e-mail addresses from those who affirmatively request to be placed on DoleInstitute.org e-mail lists, through which they may receive information about the Robert J. Dole Institute of Politics, Senator Bob Dole and his legacy.
By submitting a form on DoleInstitute.org, you are granting the Robert J. Dole Institute of Politics the right to republish your submitted content on DoleInstitute.org and other venues of its choosing. Unless explicitly stated otherwise, we will not publish your last name, street address, or email address alongside your first name with your submitted content. By uploading an image, you are granting the Robert J. Dole Institute of Politics to republish that image as seen fit.
It is the general policy of The University of Kansas and the Robert J. Dole Institute of Politics not to make personal information available to anyone other than its employees or agents who need to know that information in the course of their duties.
Correcting and updating your information:
Finally, those who have previously requested to be placed on DoleInstitute.org e-mail lists may unsubscribe by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email you receive from us.
Browser information collected on the web site:
DoleInstitute.org analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of our website. We use an external service to provide real-time reporting of browser accesses to our site to DoleInstitute.org staff and our agents. This includes page views, unique views, unique visitors, frequency of visits, and peak-volume traffic periods. We do not use this service to gather, request, record, require, collect or track any Internet users’ personally identifiable information.
We use cookies on our site to customize the experience of our visitors and to support some necessary functions. We also use cookies to better understand how our visitors use our site. DoleInstitute.org are not shared or revealed to other sites. We do not look at cookies on your machine for other sites.
Children’s privacy:
Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulation establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. Our site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13, and we have designed our site to block our knowing acceptance of information from children under 13 whenever age-related information is requested. We would remind parents that they have a duty to supervise the Internet activities of their children.
It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of information by children under 13, please do so here.
Security:
DoleInstitute.org maintains a variety of physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. For example, we use commercially reasonable tools and techniques to protect against unauthorized access to our systems. Also, we restrict access to personal information to those employees who need to know that information in the course of their duties. In addition, we work to protect the security of your personal information when transmitted via the DoleInstitute.org site by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. Your own efforts to protect against unauthorized access play an important role in protecting the security of your personal information. You should be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer, and always log out of any site when viewing personal information.
Changes to this policy:
DoleInstitute.org will revise or update this policy if our practices change, or as we develop better ways to keep you informed about them. You should refer back to this page often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes. If we decide to change this policy, we will post a new policy on our site and change the date to indicate when it was last modified. Changes to the policy shall not apply retroactively.
Copyright Robert J. Dole Institute of Politics, 2014.
Robert J. Dole Institute of Politics2350 Petefish DriveLawrence, KS 66045Phone: 785-864-4900Fax: 785-864-1414doleinstitute@ku.edu
Hours: Temporarily Closed
Copyright © Robert J. Dole Institute of Politics
